- [Instructor] So now that
we understand the project,
let's start up the application
and exercise some of the APIs
by launching the application
and invoke them via Postman.
So, on ExplorecaliApplication,
I'm gonna right click it and say run.
And we'll watch the console.
So we see it started
with Tomcat on port 8080.
Now I've launched Postman
and I'll show you that
you can import a set,
a collection API calls.
This API Demo 1 postman
collection.json file,
if you click that and open it,
I've already got it opened,
it will launch and then start
with this Explore
California API's collection.
And this is just a shortcut I've added
so you don't have to type in
each one of the API calls.
So, within the Introduction folder,
select the first one which
is Get All Tour Packages.
So here's the http call to
get all the tour packages.
Click Send.
And we see there's our tour packages,
our Backpack Cali, California
Hot Springs, et cetera.
Now, let's get all of the tours.
Here's all the details of
my Big Sur Retreat Tour,
Death Valley,
Mount Whitney Climbers Tour.
Now, if I wanna look up
a tour by a tour package
and here I provide the code
equals BC which is Backpack Cali
so that's gonna fetch just
the Backpack Cali Tours.
Next, let's create a rating.
In the body of that I'm
sending a json string.
The score is five.
The comment was, "I thought it was okay."
And the customer ID is eight.
And this would be for the
tour with the ID equal one.
Send that that post method and let's see.
The results was that that was created.
Now let's look up a rating.
Let's call the tours
slash 1 slash ratings API
which will get all the
ratings for tour one.
And there's the one we just created.
Let's get the average score for a tour.
And the average score was five.
And let's update a
rating with the put verb.
So, we're going to update the tour rating.
Have customer four who
thought it was not that great
and a score of one.
This has been a very quick overview
of our starting point code base.
If you have access to the exercise files,
I really encourage you to take the time
to familiarize yourself with it.
Good developers are always
looking to improve their code.
So, developer, we know this
is not production ready.
How can we do better?